(Leonard:)How did she get you to do yoga?
(Sheldon:)Well, to be honest,
I thought she said "Yoda."
(Penny:)I'm helping him relax because,
unlike you, he supports me.
(Leonard:)Oh, How many times
do I have to say it?
(Leonard:)-I support you.
-Sheldon, take a break.
(Sheldon:)Namaste.
(Penny:)Okay, if you support me,
what was with that phone call?
(Leonard:)Fine. I'm not sure
you should have quit.
(Leonard:)But if you care so
much what I think,
(Leonard:)why didn't you ask me
before you did it?
(Penny:)Oh, so now I need
your permission?
(Penny:)Would you have asked me
before you quit your job?
(Leonard:)Yes. I thought we were
in the kind of relationship
(Leonard:)where we make decisions together.
(Leonard:)If I'm wrong,
then maybe we need to talk
(Leonard:)about the kind of relationship
we're actually in.
(Penny:)Yeah, well, maybe we do.
(Sheldon:)I'm willing to if you guys are.
(Leonard:)Can we please
have some privacy?
(Leonard:)No.
(Sheldon:)I'm as much a part of this
relationship as you two,
(Sheldon:)and I think it's high time we
put all our cards on the table.
Yeah. For example,
where is this going?